This is me, right now, next to Nagoya Castle.
This is the side of Nagoya Castle.
It's cold.
It's so cold.
Even though it's April.
It's morning.
It's getting warmer.
I'm looking forward to it today.
I want to buy some candy.
Today.
I'll get right to it.
On location.
Yes, today is...
11th anniversary of my debut on the street
Location
Commemorative location
That's right.
But I really haven't heard anything about what we're doing.
I don't know anything.
Good morning. Good morning.
Suddenly.
Do you know why we're all here today?
We're on location.
Do you know what we're filming?
It's the 11th anniversary of Chiyocho's debut!
Eleventh anniversary!
That's right!
Did you see Nagoya Castle?
I did!
You're the first one to talk.
Yes, I did.
This year.
We're going to do something big at Nagoya Castle, aren't we?
Happiness.
That's right.
On the 22nd of July
We're finally going to perform "Sachi-sama" at Nagoya Castle.
I thought it would be great if we could start filming here today.
No!
It's where you'll be making your street debut today.
That's right.
Actually, today...
We have a guest with us today.
May I invite him?
Sure.
Well, I'm sorry, but I was hoping you could come.
Who?
You.
Oh, shit!
I'm going up!
Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God!
It's going up so high!
Isn't this crazy?
It's amazing!
I've had a great day!
I'm so happy!
I'm having a heart attack!
Hearts!
Isn't it bad?
Oh, my God!
[preview]
Oh, no!
Wait a minute! This is too much!
Good morning!
What a surprise!
It's Mr. Nom!
Wow! Oh my God!
Please, someone, please explain this person to everyone in the video!
This is Mr. Nom, who used to watch Shachihoko when it first debuted on the street.
This is Mr. Nom from Warner who used to watch Orca Hoko when she was making her debut on the street!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Nom-san is wearing this Aloha shirt and sunglasses, just like he did back then.
Same as ever!
It's 12 degrees today! Are you okay?
It's not good.
You met Mr. Nomura recently, right?
Dinner! Come and have dinner with us!
Wanner, you know, we graduated.
All the staff who have worked for Wanner up until now...
We had dinner.
Mr. Nomura came, too.
That's right.
Even back then...
I think we talked about our memories from back then.
I think we talked a little.
April 7th?
Do you remember?
Yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no, but it's great.
Do you remember?
What?
I don't know.
Can I be honest?
It was cold.
Oh, forget it.
It was so cold.
About as cold as today.
That's crazy.
I don't know how everyone here was dressed so lightly.
It was really cold.
There was an award show, so...
That's right.
But there were so many people there.
I was so surprised.
I was so surprised to hear it was your debut show.
What? Why was it so good?
We were surprised too.
We're really happy for you.
I remember you remember us.
I thought it was cold.
But you were in middle school then?
We were all in middle school.
Junior high, right?
That's right.
No, no, no. We're all grown up now.
It's been 12, 11 years since then.
Just so.
Just like that.
It's amazing.
You grow up so fast.
You haven't changed a bit, have you, Nobe?
Remember our conversation at the dinner party?
Seriously?
I don't remember any of it. What?
Really?
I've been thinking about it ever since you showed up.
That's what you're talking about?
Isn't it late?
What?
You wanna go over there?
I just figured it out.
I don't know where we're going.
What did you do? What did you guys do?
I had dinner.
Is it coming true? What?
We had dinner.
Which one?
Wait!
We talked about this a lot, didn't we?
There's the main one.
I remember the moment it came out.
Nomura-san said, "Let's go together.
The one you suggested?The one that Mr. Nomura proposed?
What was it? Where did you suggest we go?
What did you do?
Fortune-telling.
The youth merger.
Really?
That's this way.
We were talking about a staff member who had been helping us with that for a long time,
He told me that his current job is making wine at a YouTube store,
Nagano Prefecture.
Nagano, he said.
He told me that he was making wine,
I tried to call him at that time, but I couldn't get through,
I wanted to buy wine so badly, and the wine was so famous that you couldn't even buy it.
What did I hear?
That was it.
I don't remember what Mr. Nomura told me,
I don't remember what Mr. Nomura told me, but he was in charge of orcas at the time,
I heard that he was in charge of orcas at the time, and he was really torn between choosing wine and orcas.
So now.
He seems happy.
That's how happy we are.
I don't know yet.
We don't know yet.
We haven't decided yet.
That's all we can do.
If Mr. Nomura is here, that's all we can do.
There's a remote set, right?
There's a reel here.
You're not here, are you, Nomura-san?
I'm surprised.
Is that it?
Yay!
I thought for sure you wouldn't make it.
Who is this staff member's name?
Mr. Hase.
Everyone came to see Ms. Hase today.
Yay!
I'm so happy!
That was fast!
I'm so happy to see you.
Tears.
Wait!
Oh my god!
I'm so happy!
Oh, my gosh!
I'm about to cry even though I haven't seen him anymore.
Not at all.
I'm about to cry even though I haven't seen him.
That was quick.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I looked up something. I checked your website.
And it said that they don't do interviews.
So I thought I couldn't go.
The face that came out didn't change.
That's right. The face on the website didn't change.
It didn't change.
Oh no!
Mr. Hase told me that he would love to work with orcas.
You're crying.
Why? Probably because it's too early in the morning.
Can you drink wine?
I can!
What's there not to drink?
Isn't the ban lifted?
You drink!
You were so adamant!
I drink!
I'm 25 years old!
I turned 25 at work.
You're late.
It's a good opportunity.
And congratulations.
I'm glad.
Let's go! Let's go!
It's cold, isn't it?
Are you okay?
You want me to go empty-handed?
Of course not.
But we'll take the wine.
After all, we will give it to you.
That's right.
What are you asking?
I'm just going to buy it.
It's good manners.
Where are you going?
To a convenience store.
Care to be careful?
It's fine.
All right.
I'll see you at your favorite store.
Drive safe. I'll be there.
Please do.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy to see you.
It's nice to see you, too.
How long has it been?
I don't know how long it's been since I've seen Hase mom.
Real close to 10 years.
I don't think so.
Mr. Sasama calls you by your letter.
Yes, she is.
Then you're better.
Mr. Sasama...
What?
He led us here.
What? We're both laughing.
That's right.
So... aren't you and Nomura and Sasama a pretty emo pair?
Emo.
That's really good.
I'm amazed he chose wine.
Wine is cool.
And it's great that it's become so popular.
And you got there just in time to say bye-bye.
I thought you said you were a farmer then.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I don't think you'd get it
Even if I explained it properly, they wouldn't understand.
They're in middle school and high school.
You're a high schooler now.
He's a high schooler now.
I'll have to give him a super tough time.
I'm not going to do it.
Oh, my God. He's under the influence of wine.
Oh, my God. He's so calm.
What if he's turning a little sexy?
Oh, my God.
That's so funny.
It's so funny.
It's the most different part.
It's the tone of voice.
It's like you're a mom.
It's like a mom.
She is a mom.
I used to call her Mom.
Toss has become so dandy-like.
She's growing some hines.
I'm so excited.
What do you mean, diagonally to the left, facing forward?
Is there such a direction?
The left side of the road looks hard.
Why are we going that way?
Diagonal forward left.
What are you talking about?
It's not that easy.
Diagonal left.
Is it left or right?
This way.
It's not that hard, is it?Not too hard?
A little more.
Oh, that's it, isn't it?
I see it, sir.
The sign.
I see the sign.
Oh!
Yukimura?
Yukimura? The main store?
They have "Strawberry Daifuku"!
Yabo
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I want to buy some good momos too!
I want to buy
I want to buy all kinds of things!
If you're going to go to all this trouble...
Oh, you mean they have both Japanese and Western sweets?
Snacks for the road
Fish.
Isn't this amazing?
Oh, man.
Exciting!
Wow, wow, wow!
Inside are souvenirs from Chozanmae
I want to eat strawberry daifuku!
I'll buy some strawberry daifuku too!
A hearty mouthful!
Strawberry Daifuku
Ah!
this, this
Strawberry is here!
Oh, they're here!
Shall we go in then?
Hello.
Welcome.
Where did you come from?
Come to the show.
Yes, I'm here.
Yes, you came.
At the show?
After the show.
Yes, of course.
It's been a while.
The day after tomorrow. Thank you.
May I say hello again?
Yes, ma'am.
Nice to meet you. We're...
Seino.
Super Tan Strong Enzagie
Positive Exciting Soul
From Nagaya Team Shach
Pleased to meet you
Sorry to disturb you.
We collaborated with
You know...
Orca is inside.
Thank you so much for decorating it.
Thank you for giving it to us.
There are so many!
What should we do with them?
Okay, then...
The rest is yours.
That's right.
We have to choose.
Which one do you like?
Which is the most popular souvenir?
I'd have to say...
The number one killer whale is inside, too.
It's the most popular.
Yes, yes.
The second most popular is...
There's a killer whale pie.
That's it.
Let me show you.
Chestnut pie.
Looks delicious!
Bralin.
It's true, it says "Apple" on it.
Apple
Yum!
Yay! It's delicious!
I'll have a killer whale inside, too.
What do you think? You want a killer whale pie?
Let's do it.
That's so good.
Okay, I'll have a killer whale inside.
Six of them.
And a six-pack of Kinshachi pie.
One each, please.
And...
I'd also like to try some of our
I'd love some.
Okay?
I'll start with those two.
Okay, let's take a look.
I'll take a look.
You have pastries, too?
Yes, we do.
Wow, we're almost there.
Strawberry Daifuku!
Strawberry Daifuku.
Amazing!
Daifuku Strawberry Daifuku.
It's so soft and flabby!
Strawberry Daifuku
Two.
And easy to eat... in the car.
Three.
And...
I'll have a killer whale inside, too.
I want the orca inside, too.
You want some warabimochi?
Yes, I do.
Four bracken cakes.
This way.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Please.
Hello. - Hello.
You look just like him.
He's so cute.
Do you want to take a picture with me?
You look just like him.
You look exactly the same.
No, no, no, no.
You're smiling.
You're showing me your blush.
What?
I'm Hiroba.
Hiraba.
Hiroya.
It's so cool.
Hiroba?
Broadleaf?
It's cool.
I'm Hiroba.
It's a broad leaf.
Orca's in there, too.
I'm nervous.
Nervous
Hiroyasu.
Who do you like best?Who do you like best?
I want them all.
I'm so happy.
My dad.
I'm so happy for you.
I'm so happy.
Oh, no.
Killer whale pie and killer whale pie.
and strawberry daifuku!
Three.
Good choice!
Good choice.
Too cute!
Come here.
I'm looking forward to it.
I mean, I've already had bracken cakes and tokimochi.
I ate them all.
I ate them all fast.
What? What?
I got caught off guard at the Chunichi Shimbun.
Oh, I see.
20 kilos.
Yes, sir.
300 kilometers?
Okay, then.
Okay.
We're going to Tokyo!
Nagano's a big place.
It's long.
I'll take care of it.
You don't have one, do you?
You don't have it
It's not there!
It's not showing up on my iPhone anymore.
It's not showing up?
It's only up to Alpine Village.
I'm so far away from here.
You're right.
That's what I'm getting at.
I can't find out where he is.
It's just... I can't see you.
I can't get to him.
You see that?
It's all right, as long as it fits.
Got it.
Why are you making so much noise?
Oh, food.
Earth Daifuku.
You want some of this? Let's eat first!
Let's eat!
I'm sorry to bother you, but Japanese sweets taste better when they're freshly made.
Yes, what's that over there?
What is this?
Strawberry Daifuku.
I'll start with the Daifuku with strawberries.
First, Yuzuki, give it to Haru-sama.
Harusama won't eat it.
Haru, Yuzuki will bring it to your mouth.
Oh, you can use that signal!
Get it first before Nao takes it!
Get it before Nao gets it!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
We only have four today.
I won't come if you take them.
Please don't take them!
Strawberry Daifuku!
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
Like baby hockey sticks!
I even looked up the name!
I thought I'd go buy some myself.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's sticky.
Ya-ha?
Yeah, it's delicious.
Yum.
This is the best.
I want some bracken, too.
Yes, I do.
When you say "bracken," the animals come out.
I want to take a video of you eating strawberries.
Oh, I'll take a video too.
I'll do it.
Can I take a video? When they're eating.
Oh, he's going to eat it.
Don't do that, Nee-chan!
Strawberries!
Hold this one too.
Oh, my gosh!
Hey, Ramu!
How should we eat this?
Hold it.
You're just going to take a bite, right?
Put it in your mouth and make a pretty face.
Aren't you beautiful, Na-chan? Tayutayu!
Tayutayu!
Make a pretty face!
Pretty face!
Delicious!
Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum!
You really said it in one bite.
Yeah, I know.
I know this isn't private at all.
It's private!
I've never been to Nagano before.
Really?
Maybe it's my first time, too.
I've only been on tour.
Oh, really?
Me too. I've never been to Nagano.
You've never been to Karuizawa?
O-chan, Naoto.
Oh, no, you've erased it from your memory.
Well, that was mostly Gunma.
Oh, I see.
You didn't think it was Nagano? Karuizawa.
A short walk and you're in Gunma.
Oh, right.
Nagano, though.
That's right.
Yuzuki, you went to Univa with Nao.
A year later, we went to Univa in Haruizu.
It's so different.
Yuzuki's new to Univa.
She left it to both of us.
So, you know, I thought, "Oh, the way to go around is different.
It was interesting, wasn't it?
The comparison is funny.
But Univa is kind of a long town.
That's why...
That's right. It narrows it down.
Right from the start.
Where do you want to go?
I'm aiming for at least two.
Harry Potter.
Harry Potter is the most exciting.
Me too.
It was fun.
I think it's the most amazing in the 4D world.
I think it's the most amazing of all of them.
It's great, isn't it?
Yeah, it's great.
It's a great world view.
I want you to come to our target audience.
I'll sing you a song about your idols.
I don't know the right answer.
Can you sing the Harry Potter song?
No.Different songs.
You're both singing the same song, so...
Let's try it again, both of you.
I don't know the last part.
Wait a minute.
Maybe it's not what I thought it was gonna be, the first time around.
Maybe it's not what I was expecting.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
Can you put a cuss word on that?
You're crazy.
To the driver.
I don't drive like that.
Hey, guys.
What's the theme?
Love songs
Love songs.
Okay, I'll go with "I'm going to meet my mom.
Oh, okay.
Message for Chosei Mom
A message for Chang-Sheng Mom?
Yeah.
Okay, so just sing the melody backwards with me.
Okay.
I've come a long way, Mom.
I want some wine.
Haru drove.
What's going on?
He said, "What's wrong?
I wonder if it was Chosei's mom.
I told him.
I was so worried about driving that I didn't think about anything else.
She said to herself, "What's wrong?
Oh, that's funny.
Spring, you know, I'd put lyrics to the outro of "It's a Good Life".
What was it?
I'm here.
You haven't told everyone that yet, have you?
It's a first.
Okay? First time here?
Yeah, it's good.
I guess it's time to play some good living music live for the first time in a long time.
Yes, that's right.
I was listening to the song in the order of the rehearsal? When I was listening to the song in the order of the performance,
It sounded like singing,
It sounded like a song, but it sounded like it had lyrics on it,
I'm being sued.
I'm here now.
It's funny to see the members' pretense after it's been spinning around in my brain.
Isn't it a psychic phenomenon that you're being accused of?
Yes, it is.
After you tell it to me,
I remember it when it plays there.
The lyrics come out.
I think that from now on, when people hear about the good life, they will start to listen to the song.
Now that I'm allowed to put it out, I'm going to sing it.
It's a certain thing in me,
Was it "Otome"? If you sing the interlude of either one, you'll end up singing one or the other.
That's the play.
Which one?
If you sing "Sokoplay", you become a maiden.
You'll become Sore Sore Shachi's Sore Sore Play.
Look!
I've become a girl.
It's so hard to do.
When we do the choreography of Sore Soko Menmen while singing by ourselves, we definitely turn into a maiden.
I can't do it.
I don't know where I become a maiden.
I think it's pretty early on.
In terms of performance.
I'm becoming a maiden from this point on.
What?
Sore Sore Shachi's Sore Sore play.
There, there Shachi's there play.
If you don't have enough reactions, it's not correct. Let's try it.
That's dangerous.
I don't know what's right.
I'm screwed.
What's right after that?
It's an appeal!
That's about right.
I think we can take a breather.
What was that?
I don't know what's right.
You're a girl, right?
Come on, just a little bit.
Excuse me.
Appeal
Oh, here it comes!
No, I'm going to learn to sing this.
Wow, that's great!
There's so many times. There's so many places to go.
Let's do it again. Let's all try again.
Let's do it all again.
2 Sesame
For example
Accompaniments
Not good.
Not good at all.
Seriously?
I can't do it.
Do you want to sing? Okay, no sound.
Let's join in right away.
All the way to the premiere.
Want to try singing? Okay, no sound.
I'm going to eat some bracken.
They're so good.
I'll have some too.
Which is smaller, the strawberries or the strawberry Daifuku?
Strawberries.
It's so human.
They're so human.
Aren't they delicious?
Touch it and put it in your mouth if you like.
Can I touch it?
Hold on a second.
Suck it, suck it, suck it.
I shoved it in.
You're funny.
Smoke.
Oh, no!
I'm surprised to hear you say that
I'm surprised
You've got that much of a breakthrough
Ho-chan's funny.
Smile.
I didn't even do anything.
It's overwhelming.
Let's rank them.
Wait, wait, wait.
They're all at a good level.
Basically high.
There's no one who isn't a sukibe.
But they're all out of their league.
I'm not...
I don't go around touching people's asses.
A sukibe is...
Woo...
You're so tight.
Not a sukibe episode.
HANAKA doesn't share anything
That's why I don't share it
I'm sure someone will think of something.Anyone else think...
It's not sukibe if you share it.
I don't think so.
It's so much nicer that way.
Maybe I'm the grandma who shared.
How do you know?
I can see it in your face.
You know how we talk about it afterwards?
You know, like...
It's like...
It's like he was secretly thinking about it.
It's too funny.
There are so many great characters.
There are so many characters, and they just keep coming up.
People keep adding characters.
I don't like it, because they keep coming up with them.
I'm not showing them.
So, the winner of the dirty ranking is...
Congratulations!
It's Yuzuki!
It's Yuzuki.
Yuzuki's super open.
That's right.
It's not dirty because it's super-super-open.
Oh, yeah, dirty? Lewd?
Even if it is...
Wait, what do you mean, "dirty"?
Read it.
Oh, you see, it was me.
But it means a person who is abnormally curious about the opposite sex.
Also refers to a person who...
No, it's not.
Heterosexual, heterosexual
Skeevish.
I've got a "sukebee" in my mouth.
Skebebe?
You mean a "sukebee"?
In a story about a warlord.
Well, then, let's just call him Sukebee.
Skebehe?
No, no, no!
Skebebe.
No, it's "sukebebe".
Oh, you're a "sukebebe"?
No, I'm a "bamboo" warlord.
I'll have lunch.
Willow's.
Restaurant.
Mr. Suehiro.
Traveling is fun, isn't it?
Yes, yes...
I've already made it a trip.
Journey, journey, journey...
300km is a trip
You're in Nagano.
Where are you now? We're not even halfway there. Halfway?
About 50 kilometers?
A little.
159 kilometers to go.
Yes! Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Looks good.
I have to take these off every time.
Kay-chan set meal
Looks delicious
Specialty?
It's a specialty of Gifu, isn't it, Kei-chan?
Chicken Miso
Kei-chan
Haru
Miraculous co-starring
I said so myself
Miracle co-starring
Kay-chan
Haru-chan
Kay and Kono
Nao joined in
Kay and Yuzuki
Kay-chan
Bon appétit!
Now, let's eat with Kay.
This is going to be a great meal!
Oh, man, this is good.
I'm going to gobble it up!
Riff's specialty!
It's so English!
It's too good!
Delicious.
Warm.
Warming.
Mmm. Delicious.
Mmm.
Warm.
Yes, very tasty.
Mmmm, delicious.
Delicious.
Just as I'm eating it, it comes out.
The meat.
Warms you up.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Delicious!
It's great!
How about you, Nao-chan?
Hey, Kei.
This way.
You look like her.
What's the resemblance?
It's funny.
Haru.
Kei
Nao
Let's take a picture of Nao and Haru's cars!
Keikin
Keikin and Haru's Commuter Cars
Kei-chan and Haru's Commuter Cars
It's complicated.
My member
funny
Slowly but surely
Pokemon fortune-telling
Let's try it again.
I will... later.
Not that there's anything wrong with Riff.
I just want to be a more cheerful Pokémon.
I want to be Laplace or something.
I don't know.
Not like Meowth.
I got it once.
With Meowth.
Nassy.
I remember getting a Nassy and a Meowth.
That's right.
Haru is a little different, too.
I remember we got pudding and stuff.
That's cute.
I like it.
But I don't really think you and Hou-chan look alike.
Actually, we do.
We have similar interests.
If you break it down into genres, we're the same.
Maybe we're just friends.
Maybe we just express it differently.
We're both quiet and quiet people.Because... you know... we're both quiet and quiet...
Open or not open
But we're both fundamentally the same.
You too, Izumi.
And you, too, Mr. Tafushi.
Akano-san's your favorite.
I'm sure.
We're the most like high school boys.
Manga and all that.
We have that, too.
Is that what this is about?
It's for gifted kids. It's for dirty boys.
You know...
It's like Dragon Ball or something.
That's the difference, right?
That's right.
Hey, you know what puff puff is?
Puff Puff?
I don't know.
That's not good.
Dragon Ball.
Like this?
This way?
I don't know. I've never heard of it.
I'm sure there's something like that.
There's this guy, Sameshenni.
He's very skilled, and he's always wanting to touch young girls.
To touch young girls' butts and stuff.
He says that a lot.
There's a line.
And Goku...
can tell if it's a man or a woman.
To identify whether he's a man or a woman.
I don't know.
Maybe that's what it's about?
If he's watching from Koichi, then maybe.
Maybe that's why...
That's the kind of thing that makes you giggle.
Yeah.
It's cute.
Playful.
We've never been playful like that.
I see.
Because Disney and Ghibli never came up.
It was definitely Ghibli.
Puff Puff with Totoro
Totoro.
That's right!
Footsteps Totoro?
That's right.
I have no idea
Yugi and Moto-chan...
I haven't seen Ghibli or anything like that.
It's funny and I like it.
But more than that...
I've seen Puff Puff's Dragon Ball.
I should watch Dragon Ball.
I want to be in my first semester of school there.
No, no, no...
Yuzuki's been working on it for a while.
Dragon Ball is shorter than One Piece.
But there's a lot of information in manga.
But listen... Dragon Ball takes up like two pages.
I heard.
That's why it's so fast.
To be super...
It's faster than reading 30 volumes of Hunter Hunter.
Oh, really?
And it's super fun.
Super funny.
I'm sure you can understand why they call him Piccolo...
Piccolo the egg... Oh, yeah...
like Vegeta, he's an enemy at first, but he's actually a really nice guy and he's a friend.
But he's actually a really nice guy... and he joins up with us... and the eggs...
I sold him the eggs at a bad time, but he eats them with his big mouth.
And he eats with his big mouth, so he's a reverse piccolo, which means he spits them out.
And snakes? No, not snakes.
There's a place called Planet Namek called Alien Namek.
There's a place called Namek... and the creatures there are called Namek aliens.
And Piccolo... and all the other Dragon Ball characters.
Who are the members? So there are four of them?
There are four? Four? That's too much. Someone like that?
Who is it? Tana?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one, this one.
No Freezer. No Freezer Cara Reim?
Freezer's so bad. Vegeta's the best villain of them all.
He's so cool. Vegeta's so good.
Freezer's charismatic and the kind of boss your subordinates want to be.
The ideal boss, they say. Freezer.
Not popular? He's not popular.
He's got a weird accent.
And Hal?
He's a Pappy.
You know any Pappy guys?
Yes, I do.
Trunks. Childhood Trunks.
Isn't he a real girl character?
She's a girl.
Bulma?
Not bloomers?
She's got a bra.
Or buns.
Pantsies... oh, you mean bras and panties?
Yes, and trunks, and a breezer.
I have a bra. I have a penis.
Breeza?
It's not Breeza.
I'm wearing a Breeza.
Breeza.
Pang-chan, she sure looks like a pang-chan.
Like Leigh DeLa.
My grandson.
He's so cute!
That's a kid! That's Sousuke!
No, no, no, no, no...
Come here, come here, come here.
It's a kid with food.
Oh, no!
I'm the only one who can judge you.
You're the devil yourself, Mr. Sasatan. But you're protecting Japan.
I'm not strong at all, but I'm brown when it comes to humans.
That's why.
I'm making the earth...
Yamcha!
That's so cool!
Yamcha.
You like Yamcha?
A boy?
Yamcha.
Nappa's.
When I fought Nappa.
I was like, "Hey, Yamcha, you're a naughty boy," and he was like, "No, that's just mindless.
I mean, maybe he's training in the same place, or maybe he's cutting the same path.
Where did you notice that?
I'm a little disappointed that it's not just a little bit of this, but I'm trying to keep trying, just as hard as I'm trying, but I'm a little bit down.
I'm a hard-working, hard-working person... and that's always been my thirty-second point, my guitar.
I've made the earth once, so you can do it with any other chain.
I watch a lot of old cartoons in common.
I'm very familiar with it, so I'll tell you.
I'm more interested in the ones with a lot of characters.
It's funny.
You can pick and choose.
I don't know much about One Piece.
If it's One Piece, it's easy to understand.
I see.
One Piece then.
I'm pretty much the main member of One Piece
One Piece.
You don't have to be a main memberIt doesn't have to be the main thing.
To some extent, to some extent.
Nambi.
It's a little bit like a wave.
Are you sure you want all those main spots?
Sure.
It's easy to imagine.
Like Mr. Melbye.
Oh, your mother?
I love her.
Belle.
Mr. Berubey?
Mr. Belle Merle.
Nami's.
I saw that.
It's a bad scene.
The second one.
Yes, yes, yes...
Is it easy to understand?
You're watching One Piece here?
Haru already
At first, pattachu
That's about it.
But I want you to just look at that part.
That's the only part that made me cry.
For Nami
Nami and I have another brother
For the sake of...
I became a decoy and died...
Yuzuki said it really made him cry.
At the TV station, when they were recording.
Don't you remember?
I remember. I remember.
It's all over the TV.
The one we were offering.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
It's probably the part of One Piece that makes me cry the most.
I want to explain something.
Everyone says "Chopper"...
I want to explain it.
And after that...
Luffy's straw hat... he says he won't let anyone touch it.
Nami asked Luffy for help... for the first time.
And then he puts his straw hat on Nami.
She wouldn't let anyone touch it.
It really makes me cry.
And then they became friends...
Enemies.
I'm like, "Oh, my God!" and then they become my friends.
Oh, my God.
I'm getting goosebumps.
So, who are the characters from Spring?
Chopper.
I think so.
Chopper
Always Chopper.
We've already had two.
The last time we did something like this, it was with Chopper.
Gorilla Bash.
That's right.
That's the feed.
But this place is ready.
Usopp and Brook.
It's really Brook.
Definitely Brooke.
But so am I.
I love Brook too much.
And I don't think he's in your way anymore, do you?
I'm judging her fiercely.
I'm sure he is.
Let's do Oni No Kai. Let's do Oni No Kai.
Let's do Oni No Kai!
Let's go!
I've applied the first members to the Onimizu characters.
Let's see...
Let's start with
Spring
From Spring
We're stopping for a moment.
Yes, sir.
Who was here first?
Let's see...
Inose...
Inose
Zenitsu
Sumijiro
Mr. Purgatory
Pillars, huh?
It's the Pillars, isn't it?
Depends on whether it's the pillars or those three humans.
That's for sure.
They're there too.
Like Aoi.
Aoi...
Then, from spring...
Spring...
Who
Who?
Well, it's hard to say.
But...
When it comes to the devil's death
The brave part.
What's that?
Purple. Purple.
And this is Ninja.
Shinobu-san.
If only there were some lightness in you, Shinobu-san.
I don't think it's Shinobu-san.
If you were more upright
Between Aoi and Shinobu
Between
Aoi-san...
Because she chose to go online.
of the world line that Aoi fights in.
Person
If it's her personality.
This is Ms. Scaley.
I don't know much about him, but...
Isn't he a pressure point demon?
The pressure point demon?
Demon!
Oh, hey, hey, that one.
Looks like that one, doesn't it?
Uh...
Red... like a red...
The Red?
Akiza!
Uh, Akiza?
Not like Akiza?
Akiza, more manly...
He can be a little manly.
But you know, if it's the brave part, sure.
He enjoys fighting.
Oh, wow.
Where do you want to take it, members?
Where do you want to take it?
I think Akaza is the right choice for the strong part.
Because all this time, you know..,
You call him by his first name, don't you?
Kyojiro!
It's because he has a sense of name.
But if you call him Kyojiro, then..,
Hou-chan has a theory about Akaza, too.
That's true.
But Ho-chan doesn't seem to be the type of person who uses his hands,
I don't think Ho-chan uses his hands or something.
When he fights.
What is it?
He has a weapon.There are likely to be weapons.
I can see that.
I know. Hold something,
Akaza is the type to go bare-handed.
So maybe something like that.
Who's the spider?
Louie!
If it's Louie, Nao's closer.
Louie?
That way.
I thought you said Louis was really lonely.
He's a family man, isn't he?
Yeah, a real family.
You know what I like about you?
Akaza and the others are bad.
Wasn't Akaza a family man too?
No, brother.
No, they're lovers.
I thought they were brothers.
He had a girlfriend.
We met in the middle of a relationship.
And then he died.
That's right.
But Yuzuki has that guy.
The big guy from the beginning.
Hand?
No, no, no.
In the pillar.
But he retired early.
What? I'm glad.
You're from the do-gooder faction?
I'm so happy.
What was it again?
What was the name again?
Uh-uh.
Uu-uh.
Uui
I'm so happy!
Mr. Uzui?
Mr. Yuyuu?
Seriously?
The guy with the girls?
I'm so happy.
But Yuzuki...
Yuzuki was so flashy.
Flashy.
I'm going to be flashy from here on out.
Yuzuki Uzui is my favorite!
She really is my type.
I love you too!
I kind of like Yuzuki's
Moon in Musou mode
It's Yuzuki Uzui-san, isn't it?
Finally, a really good character.
I've seen him.
Usopp and the others are good too.
And Honoka and me...
I guess it's Hou san
Which part of Hou-san do you want to shoot?
So far, he's a little bushy.
I've been watching him.
I'm going to take a picture of him with his mooja-mooja.
The cool side.
I want to pull it with the cool side.
That was Momojamo
With the momojamo.
You were pulling on it.
Mr. Marenku...
I'm here.
He was there, wasn't he?
The blind man.
Himejima.
Eguro
Oh, Himejima-san.
I like that person.
I like him too.
He wasn't a very nice guy.
He's strong, but he's not a collectible.
Even though he's the strongest.
Yuzukusa
I like Munan a lot, but he's just too much.
I understand.
You do?
That's true.
You really like it?
You know what I like about spring?
That's her, isn't it?
That's all I'm saying.
That's right.
I knew you'd say that.
Why?
Yuzuki might be my least favorite.
Doma.
I think it might be good for spring!
I'm happy.
I can do it! I can do it!
Not a bad version of Doma
I don't know...
The tension...
Maybe the brightness is the same as the horse.
It's like a swinging element, so it's good.
He's a guy who enjoys life, right?
She seems like she's having fun.
I think she'd really like spring.
You think?
It's amazing you got it right.
So far Haru and Yuzuki...
That's a close call.
Let's call it spring.
That's my horse.
Mr. Iguro
Mr. Iguro, but...
But you're a little different, aren't you?
He's got a strong habit
Yes, different
But you too...
Aren't you good?
You don't seem interested.
You're so interested in the Guan Lu people.
You think about them, don't you?
He doesn't say much.
As I recall, you're not the talkative type.
That's right.
What do you think?
I'm a man of many words.
Brock too.
Brock and Satan both talk a lot.
But they're more fiery than talkative.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Let's think about Ho-chan in warrior mode.
Maybe a baby.
She seems like a baby.
She talks a lot, but...
A baby.
A baby with a few words.
Oh, no.
I'm sure he's a good guy.
I'll tell you, Tamayo.
Tamayo?
Is there a tamayo element?
It's like a combination of Tamayo and Inoske.
Hey, it's the opposite.
Which element?
Akaza. It fits.
Akiza.
Akaza's nice.
She's the one in armored mode.You're the one in armed mode.
Isn't it because you look a little like a monkey?
You know...
She seems to enjoy fighting.
He's so strong.
Normally...
Purgatory would've given up if he was that strong.
Until the end.
In an environment where he doesn't turn into a demon.
He's a little persistent, isn't he?
Persistent.
Persistent, persistent, persistent.
You're not persistent, Inaho.
I'm not persistent.
Yuki seems more persistent.
No, she's not that clingy.
In an environment that doesn't turn you into an ogre
She'll say it all the time.
She'll say it till the end of her life.
She's gonna keep saying it.
Okay? When are we gonna eat it?
We'll say it when the sun comes up.
It's not safe.
I'll keep saying it.
Okay, I'm going in.
Yes.
That's you, right?
Who's that?
The pillar.
I've been watching from the beginning.
Nao's favorite character.
Giyu.
He's so good!
It's not Giyu
It looks like Giyu.
I'm so happy.
Isn't it on your hip? That kind of thing...
It makes me happy.
Fans say it's in her buttocks.
Akazawa... it's on your hip, isn't it? No, not at all.
Not her buttocks at all.
It's not a butt!
Where's Ho-chan's butt?
Hey, Mr. Igloo...
Are they the same?
Mr. Igloo... I saw "Mr. Igloo" on the TV.
But touch Mr. Igloo's snake.
Mr. Igloo's hips aren't hips at all.
Mr. Igloo is the one with the eyes.
But it's the other one.
That's right.
That's what Mr. Igloo means.
Hey, Hou-chan, let's play Pokemon!
Oh, I know Pokemon.
No, I don't play Pokemon
Pokemon self-analysis
No, I don't
It takes a lot of time
Then, you should do it.
I don't remember there being that many problems
Let's present it together.
Okay.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Then, do mine too!
Wow, that's hard.
Oh no, I'm not going to look at the results yet.
I'll have to look at it next time I open it.
I think I got 16 questions.
That was quicker than I thought.
I won't look at the results.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
It's different.
What's going on?
What is it? What is it?
It's Rigg.
That's weird.
Pikachu.
Heh.
That's amazing.
It's a rig.
I'm gonna tear it all down.
They're all Pikachus.
When they touch the Rin, they can't stop until they've destroyed everything in their path.
That's great.
You're just digging your way through.
You should check in with the others sometime
You want to try it?
I'm in.
Do you like looking at data and numbers?
Yes, somewhat.
More or less yes.
Are you well prepared for nature?
More or less yes
Do you get annoyed when you see people who are sketchy?
I think I like to think deeply
More or less yes
I act before thinking
I'm sure this is one of them.
I prefer to speak in conclusion.
Conclusion?
What do you mean?
Oh, you don't like it?
First.
I think like this.
Like, because.
Uh, yes.
Well, I think...
I think, because.
Mm-hmm.
It's neither of those things, I guess.
I'm often called cold.
I don't.
I don't like to waste my time.
No, I don't.
Maybe you're like me.
You have a passive-aggressive stance.
Yes, I am.
You're willing to do whatever it takes to help others.
People often tell me I am kind.
Yes, to a certain extent
I always read the situation and act accordingly
I talk to people positively even when I meet them for the first time.
Yes, to a certain extent Yes
I am always at the center of the conversation Yes
People tell me I am cheerful Yes
I often express my thoughts on my face Yes
I've got the result. I'm Kabigon.
I'm a "kabigon." And he was at my place.
Isn't that great?
Yeah, it was right here.
I think there's something about Kabigon. Pikachu and Digder.
It says here that Pikachu and Digder have opposite ideas.
I'm sure we can be good collaborators.
We can be good collaborators.
It's amazing, but there are so many ways to be.
Oh, my God, Digder, there he is again.
I've tried so many times. There's so many ways to be a Diggars.
Oh, there's a One Piece character downstairs.
No way!
Oh, I want to do that.
Wouldn't it be great if we could do that and get all four of them?
Oh, my gosh, wait a minute, I'm sending this to you guys.
I'll send it to all of you.
Oh, oh, here we go.Oh, oh, it's coming out.
It's out?
I'll send it to you.
I sent it to Izumi.
I'll ask you some more questions when I'm done.
What?
This...
There's still a few people missing.
Shall we announce it together?
Yes.
Heh heh heh heh.
Here we go.
I seriously don't know this guy.
Who?
I can see you.
Who is he?
Is he nice?
Nice guy.
Can you show the camera with your hand?
Yeah, all hands on deck.
Oh, my God! Why? Why?
What?
You're so good with the buggy.
Who is it?
Oh, my God.
The best.
Luck.
I mean, he's got a lot of capacity.
But you know what I mean.
I don't think he's like Nao.
I got Luffy.
But there's a port-a-potty, right? It's like an "e".
I got Reilly.
Isn't Reilly strong? He's so good.
He's one of Roger's pirates.
Who? And Baggy?
He's kind of an idiot.
He's kind of an idiot, but he's surprisingly strong.
Everyone thinks he's weak.
But he reigns supreme.
I'll give it a try, Mr. Sakamoto.
When Al asked the question.
What did you all answer?
It's got some pretty realistic words on it.
Tell me, everyone.
You are a pirate captain.
If you have to abandon one of your crew
If you have to abandon one of your crew for any compelling reason.
I love it.
The best fighter.
Or your best friend, the mediocre fighter.
Which would you rather have?
Which would you rather be?
I'll show my best friend.
The best, really strong fighter.
Or your best friend, the not-so-strong fighter?
Which would you rather give up?
Best friend
I don't want to give up my best friend.
I'll give up my best friend.
Have you demonstrated your best friend?
Best friend.
It's the other way around.
You think your best friend understands you.
Well, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not like I'm gonna kill you or anything.
I'm gonna put you down.
Which is more fulfilling for you?
Defeating a powerful enemy or rescuing a friend from a stronghold.
It was a friend.
I don't remember which one you chose.
Which one is your legendary...
What fascinating effect do you think One Piece, the great treasure, will have on you?
You can become invisible at will.
You can get countless treasures and money.
You can become the king of your country.
You can bring the dead back to life
I can bring the dead back to life.
What did you do?
That's a dead person.
Money.
I have money.
We parted on good terms.
As fighters on a pirate ship.
What? Izumi said you're a chopper.
I just got your LINE.
Existing
Oh!
Which captain would you rather be?
Pragmatic, strong and purposeful?
Kind, honest, empathetic.
Which is what?
Oh, I don't know.
I think I put it lower.
I don't remember.
Why did you say that?
Well, which captain do you want to be?
Captain.
That was really the hardest one.
Oh, no.
That's so sweet.
I might have picked the best captain.
I chose the gentlest one.
It's soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo hard!
I might have picked one.
Next.
If I were to compare you to an animal, I would choose
I am a deer
Whale. Whale.
Whale?
A whale, a cheetah...
I totally thought it was me.
I thought it was a deer. I thought it was a deer too.
Why are they all deer?
Wait, why are you all deer?
How do you behave when dealing with others?
Unreservedly confident
Indirectly ask how they are doing
Indirectly to me
Good for you
Which way of pirate life do you prefer?
Enjoying epic battles or a steady journey
Number 2
Me too, number 2.
Wow.
That's going to be something totally different.
Who do you think is the last boss among the characters?
An attractive young woman with red eyes, a silent, sinister man, Onwa? Ongong? Onnawa?
Like gentle.
Gentle old woman.
A simple, pretty girl with a mysterious howl
Old woman
Number 1
Old woman, I am number 1
Which of the following is more difficult for you?
Talking about your partner's faults
Using false compliments
Number B.
Really?
Number B?
It's different when you use false compliments.
Tough.
It's hard.
It's easier to say your partner's faults.
Yeah.
Huh.Huh?
Which of the following would you like to do?
Yes No
Think realistically and set achievable short- and long-term goals
Look to the future and think about the ideal life you envision
Me too1
1 idea
Did you go with two?
Yes, I did.
Where would you like to live to be born among the places where hidden treasures are said to lie?
The Magic Underground, The Windy City.
I'm having a little trouble reading this.
What's with the clouds? A lake?
Yeah.
And, you know, the ruins of the sandstorm.
Number two.
Sandstorm ruins.
Sandstorm Ruins.
Oh, we're together.
Hey, where is that?
Which idea do you want to believe?
Yes, I do.
Start spending time in solitude and be your true self.
Yes.
When you share your joy, your joy doubles and your sadness halves.
Number two. Number two.
I'm number two.
Mm-hmm.
You are an old man who has spent many years away from the tip of the dress.
How would you tell the children in your village about your adventures?
Little by little, in chronological order.
Skip the details and talk about the events that are the biggest highlights.
Number one.
I want to tell the whole story.
Number two.
Looking back on your life as a pirate, which of the following would be the most memorable episode for you?
The time I made the decision to disintegrate; the time I was recruited by three warring factions at the same time; the time I set foot on an island that no one had ever set out; the time I defeated my master after five years of hard training.
Number three.
Number four.
No, thank you...
Oh!
That's great.
Hey!
That's so good.
He said he was on his way to get it.
Steeplechase skit.
Oh, my God.
I said it's going to be a kit, and it's going to be a kit.
You'd better have eyes to see.
Don't come to these waters if you're not prepared to live or die.
Bullish!
Very strong.
Like they're going to make a brave journey.
That's what he said.
That's so cool.
I think it's very Kit-like.
It's so disjointed, isn't it?
So disjointed.
But still, you're pretty... but I guess that's why you're a buggy, right?
Baggy?
Oh, really?
I don't know.
Baggy's a great character.
Baggy is so good.
I've never seen that face before.
He's a great character.
He's got a great zest for life.
He's like, "I'm the big guy.
It's funny.
He's got a sense of humor.
Yeah, he's funny.
Yeah, it's kind of...
It's comical when it comes out.
Yes, he's an enemy, but he's also kind of...
I'm glad when he comes out.
I feel like he's not really a bad guy.
I don't think I can be bad.
Like the Bikinman.
Oh, the Bikinman.
It's getting pretty dark.
It's so foggy.
The mountains are so hilly.
It's all white back there!
Yes, it is.
The mountain road is amazing!
Wow, it's like Ghibli!
Let's walk!
Let's walk, let's walk!
I'm fine
I love to walk
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Slopes, tunnels...
Grass belly
One bridge
Sekobako jariri michi
through the clouds
the way down
lalalalalala
It's an uphill road
But it's still a long way up
If your ears are burning from the lack of oxygen...
I don't mean thin oxygen. I mean atmospheric pressure.
Air pressure.
Oh, my God.
Is Hase mom here? She's out there somewhere.
She's here. She's gonna show up.
She's hiding in the trees. I don't know how to look for her.
I'm not sure how to look for her.
If Hase Mom were here, I'd recognize her.
She seems like she'd just stand there.
There's no one around.
She might blend in with the trees.
There are so many trees.
Yeah, I'm getting nervous.
It's just a house.
Yeah, but, you know, the way it looks on the website, it's amazing... it's beautiful.
Oh, oh, here!
Did you see that tower thing in the picture?
I don't know.
Oh! But the people...
What? This place is cool.
It's very popular.
What? Mom?
The flowers are right... Here?
What? There's a person coming out!
There's a person walking out!
Oh, no? Isn't that Grandpa?
Ha-ha-ha!
That's not Grandpa at all.
No, he's not.
It's a new building.
Oh, there it is! Look at this.
It's a beautiful building.
I knew it. It's kind of fancy, isn't it?
There it is.
Isn't this it? Exterior.
Oh, wow.
Is there something beautiful there, too?
It's a little bit western... western style.
Oh, that?
It looks like that one, doesn't it?
What?
Oh! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
Aah! Out, out, out!
I'm getting it!
It's working!
Ah! There it is!
It's still fast!Let's go!
Shall we?
Oh, you're wearing wine-colored clothes.
Red wine color.
Yay!
Mom!
Who's Mommy?
That's Mommy's voice!
Mommy!
Hello!
There she is!
Thank you!
Mommy!
I'm here!
Wanna go for a ride?
Wanna go for a drive?
Oh, my God, thank you so much!
I'll just get off!
Just get off!
I'm coming!
Oh, man!
Thanks for the curry!
Thank you so much!
We're here!
Mommy!
Oh, man!
It's been a while.
It's been a while!
But you guys haven't changed!
You haven't changed!
Even Mom!
Mommy!
I'm so happy!
I'll do it.
It's Nakata.
But you were on stage.
No, no, no, no.
You were on stage.
You read us a double letter.
With the new specs and everything.
You were on stage.
New stuff.
Wow.
It's a little cramped.
The ban on alcohol is lifted, right?
The ban is lifted here.
The ban isn't lifted here.
I see.
Of course it is.
We were drinking beer at the launch.
Of course I can't drink.
I feel bad for him.
Chews... mixed with all kinds of stuff.
That's what we did.
Beer bar.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cheweses mixed together.
Oh, my God.
Like two weeks before high school.
I've been working with a lot of people from my hamburger days.
I had a chance to hang out with some of the staff from my hamburger days.
When we took turns
Hasemama is supposed to be amazing.
That's right.
Everyone was saying that.
She was so great that I couldn't even meet her.
And then they came to me and said.
Let's read up on Hassema.
Fortune-telling was booming.
A young man...
Young men...
Everybody was telling fortunes.
They came in
I said, "What's that?
I didn't hear it.
Tell me his face.
There, there.
Nameko, come here.
You've departed from Senri Choujo-jo, so here.
There are flowers over there.
Oh, no.
Amazing.
The smell.
Well, um, the club building is really simple...um, let me explain it to you now...simply.
Please do.
Hase-sensei's,
Wine class.
Yay.
Um..,
Can I go home then?
Oh, you still have it.
Isn't it amazing?
Well, maybe I want to find out,
You put this part in here, and then you squeeze the big Presley in there,
If it's a white wine, you can squeeze it and then bring it back there by its weight.
Heh.
And then you ferment it, and then you tarmac it,
Wow.
That's so easy.
To be honest, it's not that even a monkey can make wine, but wine can really ferment in just two days.
Wow.
And white wine,
So, white wine..,
White wine first, and for the red, you just mash the knee and the figs together, mash the whole skins together,
Finally, when the fermentation is finished, we crush them and squeeze them.
Then, when the fermentation is over, the wine is crushed and squeezed.
The wood is kept in the barrel for a long time,
The amount of fermentation decreases little by little every week.
Wow.
The amount of verification, or rather, the amount decreases.
Is that so? Why?
We have it fermented once a week and filled to the brim,
Three places.
And if I went to drink it every day of the week.
I'm going to go play with the bins in the early fall.
Oh, there, you see, there are lots of bins.
After you've had your bins, well, the shortest is three months.
I let them sit for at least three months and as long as a year or so.
So it's like, "I'm having lunch.
I'm just looking at it...
I think a lot of people think that winemaking is all done in this place.
But in reality, it's 70%, 80%, 80%, 80%, 80%, 80%, 80%, 80%, 80%, 80%.
But in reality, it's more than 80% farming.
Growing grapes is the hardest part.
That's where we start.
It's all in the vineyard.
Wine is wine making, it's agriculture.
People say, "Well, wine is wine making.
Grapes are better.
No, no, no, grapes are cool.
They're so cool.
No, no, no.
Why not?
When we fit the style, that's when you said you were going to do farming,
You said you're gonna do farming?
Just that way, and follow that path,
And then good luck! That's how we started from scratch, right?
That's how we started from scratch, right?
And you've made it this far in the same activities.
In 9 years.
No, no, no, no.No, no, no.
It was more farming than I imagined.
Er, a lot.
I pretty much started my own business here in Nakano San France in about 2014 or so, doing cyberlance,
I made a lot of mistakes until now,
It's in the mountains, so there are animals, grape eaters,
Mosquitoes got sick,
There were also a lot of grapes that didn't come off,
It took a lot of people to get it up and running.
It's so beautiful. It's beautiful.
At that time, I, you know, always..,
Sacchan, you know, especially the one I liked the most,
I loved Enjoy Life.
Wow! Just like that!
Listen to Enjoy Life,
I've been through a lot of things before I came here.
For 9 years, I've had a lot of help from people I've noticed.
I'm so happy!
I've been in a fainting spell for a long time,
I've been listening to "Enjoy Life" a lot.
I'm so happy!
But I really didn't have much emotional support.
I have to work hard too!
I'm glad to hear this, Airi!
Spring is going to cry!
But you haven't had wine yet!
That's it.
That's it!
I'm glad.
I want some wine.
Yes, it's all right.
I'd like to do a classy version.
It's been a while, Hase mom.
It's been a while.
Mama Hase has fulfilled such a wonderful dream, and we have celebrated our 11th anniversary.
We have celebrated our 11th anniversary.
It is no exaggeration to say that we would not be here today if it were not for Hase mom and Ms. Nomura, so we are truly grateful.
Let's keep up the good work.
I'll be there.
Are you okay? Are you following me?
I'm fine.
Say it with me. Please do.
Seino!
Sparkling cheers!
Congratulations!
Congratulations. Bon appétit.
It smells so good.
The aroma is delightful.
Wow, delicious.
It is soft.
Delicious!
Thank you.
Eh?
Oh, thank you.
Delicious!
That's good.
I've never tasted anything this good.
I don't know.
It's amazing.
It's so delicious.
My mom made it for me.
This was just juice.
Thank you very much.
It's made from grapes.
Grapes.
Something amazing is happening.
Super easy to drink.
Doesn't it smell like grapes?
Yes, it does.
It smells like lemon or grapefruit.
It's a thumbnail.
It comes from grapes.
It's amazing.
It's strange, isn't it?
No strawberry scent or grape scent at all.
Oh, without really smelling of grapes.
I think it's good that this kind of aroma comes out.
It's amazing.
I wanted to drink it.
It's easy to drink.
I wonder how much I can drink.
If I go this way and this way,
I'm not sure if it's really going to be a Berber.
The members of the group are pretty strong, so it's okay.
They are strong, aren't they?
They are surprisingly strong. Members.
Timing of progress.
Pretty color.
This is totally different again.
This has no more bubbles.
I can compare drinks like this.
It's fun. Fun.
This one is now Chardonnay, Muscat berry and Pinot Noir with strawberry-like aroma.
Lovely.
Muscat berry, Pinot Noir and Chardonnay.
Three kinds.
So it's a little lofty and strawberry-like aroma.
Delicious.
Nice aroma.
It's a nice reaction.
Thank you very much.
This is so delicious.
It's like dessert.
It's fruity.
This one here is a table wine at the right time,
Easy to drink.
They ask you to pair it with a meal.
It's good.
It's easy to drink.
My name.
Adult wine from here on.
Wow.
This one has a stronger alcohol content,
Please.
When the grape harvest is low, the sugar content is high and the alcohol content is high.
The higher the sugar content, the higher the alcohol.
The concentration is also higher.
The alcohol content will be totally higher.
Be a little bit careful.
This is why we can get a good aroma like mango or contoudo.
They all have different aromas.
The colors are really beautiful, aren't they?
Are they really all grapes?
It's all grapes.
It's very strange.
Wow. Delicious!
Thank you.
What a happy reaction.
Oh my God.
It's so good.
This is amazing.
The smell is totally different.
It's totally different.
The one you just saw is really different from the amount of grapes we harvested.
It's amazing.
This aroma is different, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
Mango?
When mangoes ripen, they have the aroma of pineapples, mangoes, and yellow peaches, not white peaches, and other ripe aromas.
But it's still only grapes.
Only mangoes.
What's going on?What's going on?
No, it's really interesting.
It's really good.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's seriously the best thing I've ever eaten in my life.
It's true.
This is really.
I don't know about all this wine, but this is the best wine of my life.
This is delicious.
It's cool.
It's good.
Because it's purely delicious.
It's important. That's very important.
Yeah.
It's something I think is important.
Who?
This is red, and you should enjoy the aroma.
The reason is that it rained a lot this year before the harvest, and the grapes that were so concentrated became a little thin,
The grapes are not as concentrated as before,
So the grapes are not as concentrated as before, but they are still delicate because of the reduced water content when it rains.
Yes, that's right. Rain before harvest is the worst.
Wow.
That's why I hope you enjoy the aroma.
Nice aroma!
In a better year like this, it would have more structure, more strength, and more flavor,
Great aroma!
The aroma is amazing!
It has a gorgeous feeling, which is why it's so easy to drink.
So it's easy to drink.
It's easy to drink.
The weather has been pretty good lately, so the grapes bloom during the rainy season.
During that time, the whole field smells of grapes,
If I say that there are a lot of grapes in the field, it is not like cherry blossoms now, but they do not fall,
But if you say there are a lot of grapes in the field, they don't fall off, but the yield drops drastically.
Grapes are such delicate things, aren't they?
Well, it's a tea disaster, so I really hope the rain in the second half of the season will stop.
A week ago I was too frustrated.
Too much frustration. It happens often.
Not at all,
Thank you.
I drank.
Are you okay? Is your face red?
Is your head red, too?
I don't remember how much I drank.
Your face isn't good enough.
Slow down!
Are you okay? Are you okay?
To be honest, the third one was the one I thought about the most.
The third one.
I loved it.
I was surprised. It was too good.
We were saying, "This is our top cube,
Even if the vineyard is the size of the Tokyo Dome,
There is a plot of land that produces good grapes.
What is it? Is it exposure to the sun?
I don't know, but the grapes that come out of those plots are delicious.
I don't know about the ice, either.
It's the little things.
Even if you do it for an area the size of Tokyo Dome, the taste is obviously different.
Is that why you chose Nagano?
I don't know the reason why I chose Nagano until I planted them,
I am not very open about it,
I was training in wine when I was managing Happiness.
I didn't tell anyone at the company,
For example, after an event in Aratama River City, I flew directly to Nagano,
I was working there for a long time.
I would go to meetings in the morning,
I would often go to meetings in the morning,
While I was training in Nagano, I thought I could make good wine in Nagano.
But of course, it was my first time here, so I didn't know what would happen,
I am still in the middle of a battle,
Too cool.
No, no, no.
Aratama River City was just getting started, wasn't it?
That's right.
We were going back and forth.
That's the kind of thing, right?
That kind of thing.
That's useful.
That kind of effort, not at all.
It's a life of flames. A life in flames.
Is that what a life in flames is?
No, no, no. Do what you really want to do.
Even so, to hear about the youth merger at the time of the Wuhan meeting,
I went through the staff, or someone who knew about it at the time,
At that time, Hashimomo was seriously considering whether to go the way of Kurumachi Soukou or wine,
I was told by someone that Hashimomo was seriously wondering which path to take, Kurumachi Soukou or wine.
Someone told me about it, and I heard about it now,
I was told by someone, and after hearing about it now, I realized that such a thing had happened.
When I saw the Budokan, I thought, "That's enough, you guys are already in a great place,
You have already gone to a wonderful place,
I have already been to a wonderful place, and I have already been allowed to work there as a temporary staff member,
Thank you very much.
I am glad. We will do our best.
I think we have a long way to go.
You gave me a lot of power.
It's really cool to be able to do what you love and to be able to pursue it,
It's really cool to be able to do what you love and stick to it, so we'll do our best.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Please listen to the last song.
ENJOY your life.
Okay, let's start in the middle.
From there.
Okay, then.
Are you with me?
Do you want to do it with me?
We'll do it together?
I'm happy to live modestly.
That's fine.
That's fine
That's good, too.
But there are some things that are a little more painful
I don't want to put up with it.
You don't either.
You don't want to put up with it either.
You've been living off the grid your whole life.
Grown-ups say it's never gonna happen.
Grown-ups say you'll never make it.
No, it's not true.
It's not true
You can have it all
The freest person in the world is a winner
The freest person in the world wins
Here we go
Enjoy life's development
Dodan Koi ha Ranmarujo
Dou-dou koi ha ranmaru-ba
Today, tomorrow, the day after tomorrow, goodbye
But goodbye
Let's dance, let's dance, let's dance
I'm not afraid of the flames
You've got to try it to get it started
We're dreaming big
Let's make some noise
Let's scream, let's skip the party
Let it go We're not done yet
I can't get enough of it
Cheers!
It's a dream, probably.
Oh no, I'm drinking wine now.
Enjoy!
I'm really, no, I'm really happy about this now.
And I really listened to it every day on Teitler.
It helped me a lot when I was feeling broken too, so,
Really, it came so great that I kind of wonder if this is real now.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
I will do my best. I will do my best.I will do my best. I will do my best.
We will do our best.
We really will do our best.
No, thank you so much already.
Are you okay, even though this is happening?
I thought maybe I was going to die.
I'm fine. No, no, I didn't think so.
He wanted to hear that song.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Let's greet each other at the end.
At Mio Mima.
Then, please meet me at Mio Mima.
What are you talking about?
Don't be flippant. Don't be flippant.
Well, I'll see you soon.
Thank you.
I'll see you today.
I'll see you.
Thank you for today.
Thank you very much.
That's all for us, se
Supercars Strong Energy
Positive Exciting
Soul Fron
South Room Team
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It's not good, right?
It's amazing.
I'm really happy.
I'm really happy. Thank you.
Mom, you're working so hard.
If it were me, I'd be really...
I'm really happy.
Mom is doing her best.
Dads, oh no.
I'll cheer you up.
We'll work harder.
I got it dad.
Thank you very much.
Delicious.
Here you go.
Ta-da!
This is for the girl in front of you.
This is it.
They're all too strong.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
About 300 kilometers.
Thank you very much.
You got here safe and sound, didn't you?
I'm going to go back to my mom.
We're here. We have arrived.
We had wine,
We talked about memories,
Really, there's so much more
I could go on and on.
No, not the reminiscing.
I was about to change my mind.
Yes, yes.
I'd like to talk about it again.
But I'm glad.
You've been a good friend to me for a long time,
You made your dream come true,
And now she's making great strides.
I'm happy.
It makes me happy.
I was happy when I heard your story,
But now that I've met you and heard your story..,
I'm really in love with what you do, so it just keeps coming up.
I want to hear about it.
I want to hear what you have to say, too,
I honestly thought it was really cool.
It's really cool.
I think that's why, you know, in the beginning
I mean, when a group is just starting out, you know, we don't know anything, you know,
We didn't know what we were doing,
But now that we're here, we're starting to understand more and more.
But now we understand more and more.
That's why you did what you did back then.
We are starting to understand that,
I can understand what they were doing for me at that time,
I can appreciate more and more what they did for me,
I feel more and more gratitude that I didn't know at the time.
More and more, more and more.
And now, after all these years,
Now, after all these years, we realize that the present is here because of the beginning.
We are more aware of the fact that we are here now because of the first time,
One of the people who created the beginning, Maasa Hayama
Maasa Hayama, who was one of the founders of this project, said, "We are going to start all over again like this.
who created the first one, is starting from the beginning again,
I think that she is doing her best
We, too,
It cheers us up,
I feel like I can do anything.
Thinking about myself.
I'm glad we were able to meet and talk at this time.
I was really stimulated.
I still have to work hard.
I felt like a very small person. I am.
So small.
You're right. There is no one who is making their dreams come true.
As a human being.
Yes, I think it's really cool that people are pursuing such things,
I think it's a blessing to be able to do what you love for a living,
It makes me feel like I can work even harder.
That's true.
It was delicious.
But this deliciousness is supporting my hard work,
To make something this delicious,
I wonder how hard he worked to make it so delicious. I did it myself, after all.
Wasn't it amazing when you took the first sip?
I think it's thanks to Maasa Hayama's work.
Maasa Hayama! I thought, "That's Maasa Hayama.
It's Maasa Hayama.
But on the other hand, if you really work on it with love, it will be understood.
I thought, "That's what it means to the person you're working with.
That's what I thought,
I learned a lot of things,
I learned a lot of things, and it was a lesson for the future.
We are going to have a one-man show at Nagoya Castle this summer on our first anniversary,
I feel like we are really going back to the limited edition.
That's right.
I feel the same way.
I'm really glad I came here today.
I'm really glad I could come in front of you, Setsu-sama.
I'm glad I met you.
Let's all do our best, Setsu-sama.
Drinking Hasegawa's wine.
I thought about it the day before.
The day before.
It's dangerous to do it right before.
Or after it's over.
I think Hasegawa is waiting for me.
That's right.
Hasegawa is waiting for me.
Many people have been supporting me. Even now.
That's really true.
I really feel that.
It's because of the past that we are here now.
If everyone has worked so hard, I want to do my best.If everyone has worked so hard, I want to do my best.
I want to make it a great success. Sachi-sama, too.
And we can finally say "I'm serious, I'm serious" out loud,
We can finally do what we want to do in an environment where we can do what we want to do.
Outdoors.
And our specialty will be here.
Even Sachi.
The chairman of the board of directors told us this when he treated us to yakiniku.
Your voice is your strength.
You are suited for it.
It's the image of a live performance,
The way you make it.
I remember the feeling of wanting to be with everyone, and I do it because of the image of the shirt,
It was difficult during this period when I was restricted from doing so,
I don't want to betray that feeling, and I'd rather not,
I don't want to betray that feeling.
I don't want to betray that feeling, but rather, I want you to think, "I'm glad I followed you during this period.
I will do my best.
You say that feelings are conveyed when you let them be.
I've learned that from you.
I would like you to receive our thoughts and feelings in many sentences.
If you come, you will not be disappointed.
We want to create an enjoyable live performance,
If you are interested in this event, please come and see us, Sachi-sama.
We are looking forward to seeing you.
Let's enjoy our first anniversary as much as we can.
Let's have fun.
Thank you very much.
It was a good day.
It was really good.
It was great.
I'm going to get some more wine and go home.
I'd love to show you all.
I'm going to show you all....it's the last time I'll be able to drink and wear a shirt,
I wonder if we'll see a lot more of it?
It's an adult shirt.
Maybe we will see some.
I see the ban was lifted on wine.
How many have you had?
I haven't counted.
There are four kinds of four.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Maybe five or something.
Six glasses of wine each.
Are you drunk?
That much.
There you go.
I'm drunk.
I can't eat drunk.
Are you saying you're strong?
I've gotten stronger. In the last five years.
I've been exposed.
Recently, we opened a Corona,
We have been having dinner together a little bit,
I've been having a lot of drinks with the staff,
The aroma hasn't changed too much, has it?
I only know that it makes you smile a little.
It's fun, isn't it?
It's a little bit fun.
It's all about making people aware of what's going on.
We are a positive group, aren't we?
They are tough, aren't they?
We are tough.
We are super tough in that area.
We are tough people.
Actually, there is this side to us.
And we're going to do a new side.
We can have five or six glasses of wine.
Even we are like drunks.
We can change our tension.
We are like drunks too,
I don't think the tension is that different from what we've seen in the driving videos.
We were rather calm.
We became a little serious.
It's okay to be serious once in a while, isn't it? It's okay to be serious once in a while.
It's the 10th anniversary.
It was worse when I was a lecher.
You were terrible.
Don't wear a jet skirt at all.
I'm just saying that now.
No, that's not it. Please say that.
Eighth anniversary, you're a lecher.
I only talk about dirty.
If you say it now, it means you want a skirt.
I'm sure they'll use it.
Please give me some white wine.
Loki's harvest this time.
Try the tea.
Souvenir.
Delicious.
Good luck tomorrow.
I'm glad.
Thanks, Mom.
Oh, man.
Mom will be happy.
I'm sorry it's not white.
I'm totally happy.
I'm glad.
On the other hand, red is the most precious one.
This is so precious.
I'm embarrassed to say.
I got some help.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you wrote "red" on it.
I'm full.
I'll do my best.
Next notice